directhomediscount.com 2013-12-15

# Privacy Policy

DirectBuy is a member organization, and the privacy of our members and those who visit our web properties is important to us.  To help you better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our information practices. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies to information obtained through this Website only. Other services accessed through other DirectBuy websites – including others websites to which we provide links – operate under their own policies, and we encourage you to review the policies on these other sites as you visit them. They may and likely will collect data from you per their own Privacy Policy or other such policy, and DirectBuy does not control these.  Additionally, by posting such a link or reference or redirect, DirectBuy is providing a convenience to you.  These do not constitute an endorsement, sponsorship, or recommendation of any kind by DirectBuy of the site, the products, the services, or the policies of the site.

By using the Website on which this Policy is found, you consent to the collection, storage, use and disclosure of information as described in this Policy.

## Information Collection

When you visit this Website, we may request that you provide us with certain personally identifiable information, such as name, address, e-mail address, phone and fax number, and other information. If you are a DirectBuy member placing an order, we may request credit card or other payment information necessary to complete your order. In addition, we may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., AT&T, Yahoo).

## Use of Personal Information

We use the personal information you provide about yourself to operate this Website, keep you posted on the benefits of your membership, to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services (e.g., membership, merchandise, or information on our events), to communicate with you about DirectBuy, our offerings, events and promotions, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings; to prevent or respond to prohibited or illegal activities; to enforce the terms of use of this Website, this privacy policy, the Membership Agreement, or the Membership Guide; to customize, measure, and improve the performance of our Websites and advertising; and to compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties. We also use this information to communicate with you, such as to contact you about your membership or account with us.

We may also use personal information for internal functions such as research, data analysis, and auditing to develop DirectBuy’s products, services, and communications with members and non-members. This information may also be used if you enter into a contest, sweepstakes, or other similar promotion. We may use your personal information to administer these programs.  

We may supplement information we receive online with information from other sources to assist us in evaluating and improving our Website and online products, programs, and services, to determine your preferences so that we can tailor our Website, products, programs and services to you.

## Use of Non-Personal Information

We use the non-personal information that we collect to improve the performance, design and content of our Websites and to enable us to personalize your Website experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze usage of our Websites, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.  The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

  * We may collect information such as occupation, area code, zip code, and locale so that we can better increase our knowledge of member behavior and better our services, products, and advertising.

  * We may also collect information about activities on our website.  This information is aggregated and used to help us provide more useful information to website visitors and to understand which parts of our website, products, and services are of the most interest.  Aggregated data is considered non-personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy

If we do combine non-personal information with personal information the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

If you provide us with an email address that is not listed in your member account information, we may permanently store that email address and associate it with your membership. 

## Disclosures to Third Parties

Strategic partners, agents and contractors to whom we provide access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to a legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of your Membership Agreement or the Membership Guide, these policies and terms, or as otherwise permitted or required by law and consistent with legal requirements. We may share your personally identifiable information with strategic partners in order to provide you with services associated with your membership or your use of this website. In addition, we may transfer information about you to a third party if we are acquired by or merged with another company.  

## Cookies and Other Technology

DirectBuy’s website, interactive applications, email messages, online services, and advertisements may use cookies and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons.  These technologies can help us better understand user activity, tell us which parts of our website people have visited, and enable us to measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches.  For additional information about the use of this technology please see the paragraphs below.   

Many of our web pages use "cookies” to enhance your experience with our Website and to assist us in providing appropriate website experiences for consumers, Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, providing this information on this Website. We use cookies on certain webpages to help analyze our webpage flow, customize the Website and advertising, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. We also use cookies to identify you and maintain your logged-in status.

We offer certain features that are available only through the use of cookies. You can decline cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of some of the features on this Website.

As is the common practice of most websites, we may gather some information automatically and store it in log files.  This information may include things like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, computer device type, internet services provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

This information may be used to examine and identify trends, to manage the site, to learn about user activity on the site, and to gather demographic information about our Members or visitors.  DirectBuy may use this information to tailor our marketing and advertising services.

Pixel tags may be used to allow us to send email messages in a format that users can read.  Pixel tags can tell us whether an email has been opened.  This information could potentially be used to increase, reduce, or eliminate messages sent to Members or prospects.
